♪ Me not working hard? ♪
♪ Yeah, right, picture that with a Kodak ♪
♪ Or better yet, go to Times Square ♪
♪ Take a picture of me with a Kodak ♪
♪ Took my life from negative to positive ♪
♪ I just want y'all to know that ♪
♪ And tonight, let's enjoy life ♪
♪ Pitbull, Nayer, Ne-yo, that's right ♪
♪ Tonight I want all of you tonight ♪
♪ Give me everything tonight ♪
♪ For all we know, we
might not get tomorrow ♪
♪ Let's do it tonight ♪
♪ Don't care what they say ♪
♪ Or the games they play ♪
♪ Nothing is enough ♪
♪ 'Til they handle love
(let's do it tonight) ♪
♪ I want you tonight ♪
♪ I want you to stay ♪
♪ Grab somebody sexy, tell 'em hey (hey) ♪
♪ Give me everything tonight (hey) ♪
♪ Give me everything tonight ♪
♪ Take advantage of tonight (yeah) ♪
♪ 'Cause tomorrow I'm off to do
battle, perform for princess ♪
♪ But tonight, I can make you my queen ♪
♪ And make love to you endless ♪
♪ It's insane the way the name growin' ♪
♪ Money keep flowin',
hustlers move beside us ♪
♪ So I'm tip-toein, ' to keep flowin' ♪
♪ I got it locked up like Lindsay Lohan ♪
♪ Put it on my life, baby ♪
♪ I'll make you feel right, baby ♪
♪ Can't promise tomorrow ♪
♪ But I promise tonight (dale) ♪
♪ Excuse me (excuse me) ♪
♪ And I might drink a little
more than I should tonight ♪
♪ (tonight) ♪
♪ And I might take you home
with me if I could tonight ♪
♪ (tonight) ♪
♪ And baby, I'ma make you
feel so good tonight ♪
♪ 'Cause we might not get tomorrow ♪
♪ Tonight I want all of you tonight ♪
♪ Give me everything tonight ♪
♪ For all we know, we
might not get tomorrow ♪
♪ Let's do it tonight ♪
♪ Don't care what they say ♪
♪ Or the games they play ♪
♪ Nothing is enough ♪
♪ 'Til they handle love
(let's do it tonight) ♪
♪ I want you tonight ♪
♪ I want you to stay ♪
♪ Grab somebody sexy, tell 'em hey (hey) ♪
♪ Give me everything tonight (hey) ♪
♪ Give me everything tonight ♪
♪ Reach for the stars ♪
♪ And if you don't grab 'em, ♪
♪ at least you'll fall
on top of the world ♪
♪ Think about it ♪
♪ 'Cause if you slip, I'm gonna
fall on top of your girl ♪
♪ What I'm involved with
is deeper than the Masons ♪
♪ Baby, baby, and it ain't no secret ♪
♪ My family is from Cuba,
but I'm an American Idol ♪
♪ Gettin' money like Seacrest ♪
♪ Put it on my life, baby (baby) ♪
♪ I'll make you feel right, baby (baby) ♪
♪ Can't promise tomorrow ♪
♪ But I promise tonight (dale) ♪
♪ Excuse me (excuse me) ♪
♪ And I might drink a little
more than I should tonight ♪
♪ (tonight) ♪
♪ And I might take you home
with me if I could tonight ♪
♪ (tonight) ♪
♪ And baby, I'ma make you
feel so good tonight ♪
♪ 'Cause we might not get tomorrow ♪
♪ Tonight, I want all of you tonight ♪
♪ Give me everything tonight ♪
♪ For all we know, we
might not get tomorrow ♪
♪ Let's do it tonight ♪
♪ Don't care what they say ♪
♪ Or the games they play ♪
♪ Nothing is enough ♪
♪ 'Til they handle love
(let's do it tonight) ♪
♪ I want you tonight ♪
♪ I want you to stay ♪
♪ Grab somebody sexy, tell 'em hey (hey) ♪
♪ Give me everything tonight (hey) ♪
♪ Give me everything tonight ♪
♪ Excuse me (excuse me) ♪
♪ And I might drink a little
more than I should tonight ♪
♪ And I might take you home
with me if I could tonight ♪
♪ And baby, I'ma make you
feel so good tonight ♪
♪ 'Cause we might not get tomorrow ♪